// Object Array quiz questions and answers 
const quizData = [
    {
      question: '1-What is the capital of France?',
      options: ['Paris', 'London', 'Berlin', 'Rome'],
      correctAnswer: 'Paris'
    },
    {
      question: '2-What is the largest planet in our solar system?',
      options: ['Jupiter', 'Saturn', 'Mars', 'Earth'],
      correctAnswer: 'Jupiter'
    },
    {
      question: '3-Who painted the Mona Lisa?',
      options: ['Leonardo da Vinci', 'Pablo Picasso', 'Vincent van Gogh', 'Michelangelo'],
      correctAnswer: 'Leonardo da Vinci'
    },
    {
      question: '4-What is the capital of France?',
      options: ['Paris', 'London', 'Berlin', 'Rome'],
      correctAnswer: 'Paris'
    },
    {
      question: '5-What is the largest planet in our solar system?',
      options: ['Jupiter', 'Saturn', 'Mars', 'Earth'],
      correctAnswer: 'Jupiter'
    },
    {
      question: '6-Who painted the Mona Lisa?',
      options: ['Leonardo da Vinci', 'Pablo Picasso', 'Vincent van Gogh', 'Michelangelo'],
      correctAnswer: 'Leonardo da Vinci'
    },
  
    {
      question: '7-What is the capital of France?',
      options: ['Paris', 'London', 'Berlin', 'Rome'],
      correctAnswer: 'Paris'
    },
    {
      question: '8-What is the largest planet in our solar system?',
      options: ['Jupiter', 'Saturn', 'Mars', 'Earth'],
      correctAnswer: 'Jupiter'
    },
    {
      question: '9-Who painted the Mona Lisa?',
      options: ['Leonardo da Vinci', 'Pablo Picasso', 'Vincent van Gogh', 'Michelangelo'],
      correctAnswer: 'Leonardo da Vinci'
    },
    {
      question: '10-What is the capital of France?',
      options: ['Paris', 'London', 'Berlin', 'Rome'],
      correctAnswer: 'Paris'
    },

    {
        question: '11-Who painted the Mona Lisa?',
        options: ['Leonardo da Vinci', 'Pablo Picasso', 'Vincent van Gogh', 'Michelangelo'],
        correctAnswer: 'Leonardo da Vinci'
      },
      {
        question: '12-What is the capital of France?',
        options: ['Paris', 'London', 'Berlin', 'Rome'],
        correctAnswer: 'Paris'
      },
    
  ];